Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Central Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Central Files
  - 2011/2012
    - Alphabetical Files
      - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 594)
      - North Campus (Box 594)
      - North Campus Research Complex (NCRC) (Box 594)
      - Officer Education Programs: Navy (Box 581)
      - Peer Institutions (Box 594)
      - Pfizer (Box 594)
      - Phi Kappa Phi (Box 594)
      - President
        - General, 2 folders (Box 594)
        - Accreditations (Schools and Colleges) (Box 581)
        - Appointments (Box 594)
        - Center for Ethics in Public Life (Box 594)
        - Provost Meeting Notes (Box 594)
        - Students (Box 581)
      - President's Advisory Group (PAG) (Box 594)
      - President's Council (PC): State (Box 594)
      - Provost's Advisory Committee on Internationalization (PACI) (Box 594)
      - Provost Advisory Council on Women's Initiatives (PACWI) (Box 594)
      - Provost's Campus Leadership Program (PCLP) (Box 594)
      - Provost Faculty Advisory Committee (PFAC) (Box 594)
      - Provost Faculty Initiative Program (PFIP) (Box 581)
      - Provost's Faculty Dinner (Box 595)
      - Provost's Foundation Strategy Group (PFSG) (Box 595)
      - Provost's Seminar on Teaching (PSOT) (Box 595)
      - Regents
        - General (Box 595)
        - Communications, Appointments
          - A-H (Box 595)
          - I-R (Box 595)
          - S-Z (Box 595)
        - Communications, Non-Appointment (Box 595)
      - Registrar (Box 595)
      - Research
        - General, 2 folders (Box 595)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
      - Residency (Box 599)
      - Residential College (Box 595)
      - Retention (Box 599)
      - Rhodes (Box 595)
      - Roads Scholars (Box 595)
      - Salary (includes Gender Salary Study update) (Box 595)
      - Scholarships and Fellowships (Box 595)
      - School for Deans (Box 595)
      - Science, Technology, Engineering, and Math (STEM) (Box 595)
      - Scientific Club (Box 595)
      - Secretary of the University (Box 595)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 595)
      - Sexual Orientation: LGBT (Box 595)
      - Shipman Society (Box 595)
      - SMORES (formerly Resource Allocation Group, or RAG) (Box 595)
      - Standard Practice Guide (SPG) (Box 595)
      - Steelcase (Box 595)
      - Strategic Planning (Box 595)
      - Students
        - General (Box 595)
        - Deceased (Box 595)
      - Student Affairs
        - General (Box 595)
        - Provost Meeting Notes (Box 595)
      - Student Budget Advisory Committee (SBAC) (Box 595)
      - Surveys (Box 596)
      - Sustainable Systems (Box 596)
      - Taubman Governing Council (Medical School) (Box 596)
      - Third Century Initiative (Box 596)
      - Treasurer's Office (Box 596)
      - Tuition (Box 596)
      - Unions (Box 596)
      - United Way (Box 596)
      - University Library
        - General (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
      - University Musical Society (UMS) (Box 596)
      - Washtenaw Community College (Box 596)
    - Schools and Colleges
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
        - General (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
      - Art and Design, School of
        - General (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
        - Students (Box 599)
      - Business School
        - General (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
      - Dearborn (Box 596)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (includes Accreditation documents) (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
        - Students (Box 590)
      - Education, School of
        - General (includes Facility Master Plan) (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
        - Students (Box 599)
      - Flint (Box 596)
      - Information, School of
        - General (includes Accreditation documents) (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
      - Kinesiology, School of
        - General (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
        - Students (Box 599)
      - Law School
        - General (includes Accreditation documents) (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 596)
      - Life Sciences Initiative (LSI)
        - General (includes Accreditation documents) (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
      - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of (LSA)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 596)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 597)
        - Students (Box 599)
      - Medical School
        - General (includes reaccreditation), 2 folders (Box 597)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Medical School Master's Degree (Box 597)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 597)
      - Music, Theatre, and Dance, School of
        - General (Box 597)
        - Accreditation, 3 folders (Box 597)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 597)
      - Natural Resources and Environment, School of
        - General (Box 597)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 597)
      - Nursing, School of
        - General (Box 597)
        - Accreditation, 2 folders (Box 597)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 597)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - General (Box 597)
        - Accreditation includes CD (Box 597)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 597)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General (Box 597)
        - Accreditation, 2 folders (Box 597)
        - Accreditation-Dietetic Internship (Box 598)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 598)
      - Public Policy, School of
        - General (Box 598)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 598)
      - Rackham Graduate School
        - General (Box 598)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 598)
        - Review Letters (Box 598)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General (includes Strategic Assessment), 2 folders (Box 598)
        - Appointments (Box 599)
        - Provost's Meeting Notes (Box 598)
    - Chronological FIles
      - August -December 2011, 10 folders (Box 601)
        [Personnel records restricted until July 1, 2042 ]
  - 2012/2013
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 602)
        [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2033 ]
      - Academic Affairs, Office of (OAA 6+1), 3 folders (Box 602)
      - Academic Multicultural Initiatives, Office of (OAMI) (Box 602)
      - Academic Program Group (APG), 3 folders (Box 602)
      - Academic Program Group: Budget Subcommittee (Box 602)
      - Academic Program Group: Development Subcommittee (Box 602)
      - Academic Program Group: Operations Subcommittee (Box 602)
      - Accreditation (Box 602)
      - Administrative Services Transformation (AST) (Box 602)
      - Admissions, Office of (Box 602)
      - Advance (Box 602)
      - Affiliation Agreements (5 of 11), 5 folders (Box 602)
      - Affiliation Agreements (6 of 11), 6 folders (Box 603)
      - Alumni Association (Box 603)
      - ArtsEngine (Box 603)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 603)
      - Association of Public and Land Grant Universities (APLU) (Box 603)
      - Astronaut Scholarship Foundation (Box 603)
      - Athletics (Box 603)
      - Audits (Box 603)
      - Audits Reports, 2 folders (Box 603)
      - Awards: General (Box 603)
      - Beckman Young Investigator Award (Box 603)
      - Benefits (Box 603)
      - Bentley Library (Box 603)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 603)
      - Budget and Planning, Office of (OBP) (Box 603)
      - Budget: General (Box 603)
      - Campus Safety (Box 603)
      - Capital Projects (Box 603)
      - Carnegie Foundation (Box 603)
      - Center for Healthcare Research & Transformation (CHRT) (Box 603)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT), 2 folders (Box 603)
      - Center for the Education of Women (CEW) (Box 603)
      - Central Student Government (CSG) (Box 603)
      - Chief Financial Officer, Office of (CFO) (Box 604)
      - Clements Library (Box 604)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 3 folders (Box 604)
      - Community Service (Box 604)
      - Conflict (Box 604)
      - Consultants, 5 folders (Box 604)
      - Convocation (Box 604)
      - Coursera (Box 604)
      - Cultural Collections Council (Box 604)
      - Depression Center (Box 604)
      - Development, 3 folders (Box 604)
      - Diversity (Box 604)
      - DOW Chemical Corporation (DOW) (Box 604)
      - Dual Careers (Box 601)
        [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2043 ]
      - Duderstadt Center (Box 604)
      - Economic Dinner Group (Box 604)
      - Emergency Planning (Box 604)
      - Environmental Sustainability Executive Council (ESEC) (Box 604)
      - Erb Institute (Box 604)
      - Executive Budget Advisory Committee (Box 604)
      - Executive Officers/Vice Presidential Group (EOVPG) (2 of 5), 2 folders (Box 604)
      - Executive Officers/Vice Presidential Group (EOVPG) (3 of 5), 3 folders (Box 605)
      - Executive Vice President Benefits, 2 folders (Box 605)
      - Executive Vice President for Medical Affairs (EVPMA) (Box 605)
      - Faculty (Box 605)
      - Faculty Ombuds (Box 605)
      - Finance & Capital Projects (Box 605)
      - Financial Aid, Office of (Box 605)
      - Fitness for Duty Committee (Box 605)
      - Football Suite (Box 605)
      - Foundation Strategy Group (Box 605)
      - Freedom of Information Act, Office of (FOIA) (Box 605)
      - General Counsel (Box 605)
      - Global Health Visioning Committee (Box 605)
      - Google (Box 605)
      - Government Relations (Box 605)
      - Government: State (Box 605)
      - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) (Box 601)
        [Patient/client records restricted until July 01, 2113 ]
      - Graduate Student Research Assistant/Graduate Student Instructor (GSRA/GSI) (Box 605)
      - Graham Environmental Sustainability Institute (Box 605)
      - Grand Valley State University (GVSU) (Box 605)
      - Hathitrust Agreements (Box 605)
      - Health Service (Box 605)
      - Hospitals and Health Centers Executive Board (HHCEB) (2 of 6), 2 folders (Box 605)
      - Hospitals and Health Centers Executive Board (HHCEB) (4 of 6), 4 folders (Box 606)
      - Hospitals and Health Centers Executive Board: Finance (Box 606)
      - Information and Technology: Council (Box 606)
      - Information and Technology Services (ITS) (Box 606)
      - Institute for Research on Women & Gender (IRWG) (Box 606)
      - Interdisciplinary Faculty Initiative (Box 606)
      - International (Box 606)
      - International: MPala (Box 606)
      - Invitations, 4 folders (Box 606)
      - Keck Foundation (Box 606)
      - Knight Wallace (Box 606)
      - Lecturer Employee Organization (LEO) (Box 606)
      - Martin Luther King (MLK) (Box 606)
      - MCubed (Box 606)
      - Media Relations (Box 606)
      - Mellon Foundation (Box 606)
      - MHealthy (Box 607)
      - Michigan Campus Compact (MCC) (Box 607)
      - Michigan Daily Meetings (Box 607)
      - Museum of Art, 2 folders (Box 601)
      - Musical Society (Box 607)
      - National Institute for Learning Outcomes Assessment (NILOA) (Box 607)
      - New Student Programs, Office of (ONSP) (Box 607)
      - North Campus Research Complex (NCRC) (Box 607)
      - Peer Institutions (Box 607)
      - Phi Kappa Phi (Box 607)
      - President, Office of the, 3 folders (Box 607)
      - President's Council: State (Box 607)
      - President's Advisory Group (Box 607)
      - Promotions (Box 607)
      - Provost's Advisory Committee on Budgetary Affairs (PACBA) (Box 607)
      - Provost's Advisory Committee on Faculty Mentoring (Box 607)
      - Provost's Advisory Committee on Internationalization (PACI), 3 folders (Box 607)
      - Provost's Advisory Council on Women's Initiatives (PACWI) (Box 607)
      - Provost's Council on Student Honors (PCSH) (Box 607)
      - Provost's Faculty Advisory Committee (PFAC), 2 folders (Box 607)
      - Provost's Faculty Dinner (Box 607)
      - Provost's Faculty Initiative Program (PFIP) (Box 601)
      - Provost's Foundation Strategy Group (Box 608)
      - Provost's Meeting Notes, 2010 (Box 608)
      - Provost's Meeting Notes, 2011 (Box 608)
      - Rec Sports (Box 608)
      - Regents: General (Box 608)
      - Regents: Communications, 4 folders (Box 601)
      - Registrar, Office of the (Box 601)
        [Student records restricted until July 01, 2098 ]
      - Research, Office of (UMOR) (Box 608)
      - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC) (Air Force, Army, Navy) (Box 608)
      - Retention (Box 608)
      - Rhodes Scholars (Box 608)
      - Salary (Box 608)
      - Scholarships & Fellowships (Box 608)
      - Secretary of the University (Box 608)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 608)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 608)
      - Shared Services (Box 608)
      - Shipman Society (Box 608)
      - Standard Practice Guide (SPG) (Box 608)
      - Student Life, Office of (Box 608)
      - Student Budget Advisory Committee (Box 608)
      - Students: General (Box 608)
      - Students: Complaints (Box 601)
      - Surveys (Box 608)
      - Sustainable Systems (Box 608)
      - Taubman Governing Council (Med) (Box 608)
      - Teach for America (Box 608)
      - Third Century Initiative (Box 608)
      - Tuition & Fees (Box 608)
      - Undocumented Students (Box 608)
      - United Way (Box 608)
      - University Library (Box 608)
      - University of Michigan Health System (Box 608)
      - WitsOn! (Box 608)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Architecture & Urban Planning (Box 609)
      - Art & Design (Box 609)
      - Business (Box 609)
      - Dentistry (Box 609)
      - Education (Box 609)
      - Engineering, 2 folders (Box 609)
      - Information (Box 609)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR) (Box 609)
      - Kinesiology (Box 609)
      - Law (Box 609)
      - Literature, Science, and the Arts (LSA), College of, 4 folders (Box 609)
      - Life Sciences Institute (LSI) (Box 609)
      - Medicine, 4 folders (Box 609)
      - Music (Box 609)
      - Natural Resources & Environment (Box 610)
      - Nursing (Box 610)
      - Pharmacy, 2 folders (Box 610)
      - Provost's Meeting Notes, 2011 (Box 610)
      - Public Health (Box 610)
      - Public Policy (Box 610)
      - Rackham (Box 610)
      - Rackham: Budget, 2 folders (Box 610)
      - School of Music, Theatre, and Dance: Accreditation, 2 folders (Box 610)
      - School of Social Work (Box 610)
- VPAA Central Files
  - Archived VPAA Website
    The 2010 series features the addition of the Archived Website subseries, which was created to preserve the office's public website over time. This subseries documents the mission, activities, policies, and individuals involved in the operation of the Office of the Provost and Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs as they are presented on its public website. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as reports and administrative documents), and information about committees, initiatives, and events. This archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at https://archive-it.org/organizations/934.
    - Archived Provost and Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs home page, 2010-June 27, 2017
    - Archived websited related to the Administration of the University of Michigan, 2010-[ongoing]